Guide to the Brooks McNamara Papers MSS 162
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VI: Course Materials and Student Papers., 69543
  Series VI: Course materials and student work.
  Although Series VI contains types of materials that are also located throughout Series I and filed thematically under specific subject headings, this box was originally separate and is organized more generally.
  - Interviews: Student interviews with popular performers., undated; 69566 (Box 33, Folder 651)
  - American Theatre/Film (SP '88): Bibliography., 1988; 69565 (Box 34, Folder 652)
  - Course Materials: Photocopies, articles, bibliographies, notes., undated; 69564 (Box 34, Folder 653)
  - Course Materials: Photocopies, article, fliers, newsletters, bibliographies, notes., 1995, 1996; 69563 (Box 34, Folder 654)
  - Course Materials: Programs, newsletters, publishers book catalogues; spring 1996 issue of "The Threshers' Review: a Magazine for Midwest Old Threshers.", 1994-1996; 69562 (Box 34, Folder 655)
  - Course Materials: Clippings, articles, photocopies, photographs, programs, newsletters, publishers book catalogues, undated; 69561 (Box 34, Folder 656)
  - Folk Festival Course (general): Course syllabi, correspondence, photocopies., 1991, 1992.; 69560 (Box 34, Folder 657)
  - Courses (unsorted): Photocopies, articles, correspondence, syllabi, bibliographies, BM notes, undated; 69559 (Box 34, Folder 658)
  - Radical and Experimental Course: Articles, photocopies, course syllabus, BM notes, student paper., 1991-1992; 69558 (Box 34, Folder 659)
  - Print Catalogues: Clippings, articles, publication and print catalogues., undated; 69557 (Box 34, Folder 660)
  - Radio - 1930s: BM notes, photocopied book chapters., undated; 69556 (Box 34, Folder 661)
  - Schechner Collection - Princeton: Princeton University Library Chronicle (Autumn 1993)., 69555 (Box 34, Folder 662)
  - Senelick, Laurence: Articles., 1991, 1993; 69554 (Box 34, Folder 663)
  - Student Papers (1972-1992, undated), 69553 (Box 34, Folder 664)
  - Student Paper (1972-1996, undated), 69552 (Box 34, Folder 665)
  - Student Papers (1973, 1992, undated), 69551 (Box 34, Folder 666)
  - Student Papers (1972-1988, undated), 69550 (Box 34, Folder 667)
  - NYU Thesis: Court Theatre 1980-1981, Susan Weinacht, 69549 (Box 34, Folder 668)
  - Student Papers (1991-1996), 69548 (Box 34, Folder 669)
  - Student Papers (1973-1996), 69547 (Box 34, Folder 670)
  - Student Papers (1973-1989), 69546 (Box 34, Folder 671)
  - Student Papers (1980-1996), 69545 (Box 34, Folder 672)
  - Student Papers [misc.], undated; 69544 (Box 34, Folder 673)